Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- New York Intellectuals Special with Joe Dorman and Ellen Willis, Part 1 [1999-043], 1999-05-16 (Box 13, Item 718_0457)
- Israeli Elections with Molly Malekar; Sephardic Song and Culture with Joe Elias and Aviva Ben Ur; Israeli Feminist, Hannah Safran; Author, Russell Jacoby [1999-053], 1999 May 30; 1999 June 6 (Box 7, Item 718_0225)
- A: Israeli Elections with Molly Malekar; Sephardic Song and Culture with Joe Elias and Aviva Ben Ur / B: INS Detainee, Lulseged Dhine; Israeli Feminist, Hannah Safran; Author, Russell Jacoby [1999-066], 1999 May 30; 1999 June 6 (Box 7, Item 718_0238)
- INS Detainee, Lulseged Dhine; Israeli Feminist, Hannah Safran; Author, Russell Jacoby [1999-038], 1999-05-30 (Box 13, Item 718_0452)
- Israeli Elections; Sephardic Song and Culture with Joe Elias and Aviva Ben Ur [1999-018], 1999-06-06 (Box 13, Item 718_0465)
- Police in Schools Forum [1999-052], 1999-06-13 (Box 7, Item 718_0224)
- Police in Schools Forum with Jesse Ehrensaft-Hawley; Schmidt Report on CUNY; Community Gardens Mark Leger and Tom Goodridge [1999-014], 1999-06-13 (Box 13, Item 718_0461)
- Riverdale School District Controversy; Interviews on Three Documentary Films (Faye Lederman Women of the World, Mark Gevisser The Man Who Drove with Mandela, and Oren Rudavsky And Baby Makes Two; Ethnic Parades and Gay Inclusion [1999-051], 1999 June 20; 1999 June 27 (Box 7, Item 718_0223)
- A: Riverdale School District Controversy; Interviews on Three Documentary Films (Faye Lederman Women of the World, Mark Gevisser The Man Who Drove with Mandela, and Oren Rudavsky And Baby Makes Two / B: Ethnic Parades and Gay Inclusion; Joan Nestle on Fragile Union [1999-084], 1999 June 20; 1999 June 27 (Box 8, Item 718_0255)
- Riverdale School District Controversy; Interviews on Three Documentary Films (Faye Lederman Women of the World, Mark Gevisser The Man Who Drove with Mandela, and Oren Rudavsky And Baby Makes Two (Partial) [1999-015], 1999-06-20 (Box 13, Item 718_0462)
- Ethnic Parades (Puerto Rican Day Parade, St. Patrick's Day Parade, Israel Day Parade); Joan Nestle on Fragile Union [1999-016], 1999-06-27 (Box 13, Item 718_0463)
- A: Randy Cohen Critique on Charitable Giving; Marcia Falk Reading / B: David Roskies on The Jewish Search for a Usable Past; Jewish Labor Bund CD In Love and Struggle [1999-058], 1999 July 4; 1999 September 19 (Box 7, Item 718_0230)
- A: Randy Cohen Critique on Charitable Giving; Marcia Falk Reading; Lorin Sklamberg with Music for High Holy Days / B: David Roskies on The Jewish Search for a Usable Past; Zalmen Mlotek on Jewish Labor Bund CD In Love and Struggle [1999-083], 1999 July 4; 1999 September 19 (Box 8, Item 718_0256)
- David Roskies on The Jewish Search for a Usable Past; Zalmen Mlotek on Jewish Labor Bund CD In Love and Struggle [1999-019], 1999-07-04 (Box 13, Item 718_0466)
- Iran with Ervand Abrahamian and Larry Cohler-Esses; Yemenite Music with Lorin Sklamberg; Food Shopping with Myra Alperson [1999-056], 1999 July 11; 1999 September 12 (Box 7, Item 718_0228)
- A: Iran with Ervand Abrahamian and Larry Cohler-Esses / B: Food Shopping with Myra Alperson; E.M. Bronner on Bringing Home the Light [1999-082], 1999 July 11; 1999 September 12 (Box 8, Item 718_0253)
- Iran with Ervand Abrahamian and Larry Cohler-Esses; Yemenite Music with Lorin Sklamberg [1999-007], 1999-07-11 (Box 12, Item 718_0428)
- Peter Novick on The Holocaust in American Life; Grace Paley Reading; Freud with Daniel Boyarin, Sandra Kiersky, and Kenneth Lewis [1999-055], 1999 July 18; 1999 August 8 (Box 7, Item 718_0227)
- Peter Novick on The Holocaust in American Life; Grace Paley Reading / B: Freud with Daniel Boyarin, Sandra Kiersky, and Kenneth Lewis (Partial) [1999-081], 1999 July 18; 1999 August 8 (Box 8, Item 718_0254)
- Peter Novick on The Holocaust in American Life; Grace Paley Reading [1999-044], 1999-07-18 (Box 13, Item 718_0458)
- Adrienne Rich Reading [1997-023], 1999-07-25 (Box 24, Item 718_0998)
- Chip Berlet on Aryan Nation; Rabbi Michael Skobac (of Jews for Judaism) on Jews for Jesus's Summer Campaign [1999-068], 1999 August 1; 1999 August 15 (Box 7, Item 718_0240)
- A: Chip Berlet on Aryan Nation; Jim Ledbetter on Public Broadcast; Call-ins about Community Radio and Pacifica / B: Rabbi Michael Skobac (of Jews for Judaism) on Jews for Jesus's Summer Campaign; Rebroadcast of 1998 Interview with Dr. Tal Jarus-Hakak (Partial) [1999-080], 1999 August 1; 1999 August 15 (Box 8, Item 718_0252)
- Rabbi Michael Skobac (of Jews for Judaism) on Jews for Jesus's Summer Campaign; Rebroadcast of 1998 Interview with Dr. Tal Jarus-Hakak (Partial) [1999-010], 1999-08-01 (Box 12, Item 718_0431)
- Freud with Daniel Boyarin, Sandra Kiersky, and Kenneth Lewis (Partial); Cindy Greenberg and Gail Zoffer of Minneapolis Jewish Community Action [1999-036], 1999-08-08 (Box 13, Item 718_0450)
- Chip Berlet on Aryan Nation; Jim Ledbetter on Public Broadcast; Call-ins about Community Radio and Pacifica [1999-022], 1999-08-15 (Box 13, Item 718_0436)
- Electronica Chanukah in August [1999-069], 1999 August 22 (Box 7, Item 718_0241)
- Electronica Chanukah in August [1999-079], 1999-08-22 (Box 8, Item 718_0251)
- Electronica Chanukah in August [1999-023], 1999-08-22 (Box 13, Item 718_0437)
- A: Riverdale School Board Controversy / B: Kansas Anti-Evolution Curriculum [1999-071], 1999 August 29; 1999 November 21 (Box 7, Item 718_0243)
- A: Riverdale School Controversy with Oliver Koppell and Charles Williams; Blanche Wiesen Cook on Eleanor Roosevelt, Vol. 2 / B: Kansas Anti-Evolution Curriculum; Jesse Ehrensaft-Hawley, Naomi Mezey, and Eric Zinner on Circumcision [1999-078], 1999 August 29; 1999 November 21 (Box 8, Item 718_0250)
- Kansas Anti-Evolution State Standards; Jesse Ehrensaft-Hawley, Naomi Mezey, and Eric Zinner on Circumcision [1999-024], 1999-08-29 (Box 13, Item 718_0438)
- Rosh Hashanah: Food Shopping with Myra Alperson; E.M. Bronner on Bringing Home the Light [1999-025], 1999-09-12 (Box 13, Item 718_0439)
- Randy Cohen Critique on Charitable Giving (Ethics); Marcia Falk Reading (Prayer); Lorin Sklamberg with Music for High Holy Days (Music) [1999-037], 1999-09-19 (Box 13, Item 718_0451)
- Randy Cohen [1999-002], 1999-09-19 (Box 21, Item 718_0940)
- Trafficking and the Sex Trade; Lisa Schiffman on Generation J.; David Lang and Ben Katchor on The Carbon Copy Building: A Comic Book Opera [1999-033], 1999 September 26; 1999 October 3 (Box 7, Item 718_0237)
- Campaign for Fiscal Equity Lawsuit; Palestinian Youth Dance Troupe; Trafficking Women [1999-035], 1999-09-26 (Box 13, Item 718_0449)
- Tom Segev on Israeli Elections [1999-085], 1999-10-01 (Box 8, Item 718_0257)
- Aaron Taub Interviews Lisa Schiffman on Generation J. and David Lang on The Carbon Copy Building: A Comic Book Opera [1999-059], 1999-10-03 (Box 7, Item 718_0231)
- Aaron Taub Interviews Lisa Schiffman on Generation J. and David Lang on The Carbon Copy Building: A Comic Book Opera [1999-060], 1999-10-03 (Box 7, Item 718_0232)
- Lisa Schiffman on Generation J.; David Lang and Ben Katchor on The Carbon Copy Building: A Comic Book Opera [1999-033], 1999-10-03 (Box 13, Item 718_0447)
- Emma Lazarus Marathon: Mike Wishnie, Shirley Romaine, New Colossus Voices, Hour 3 [1999-077], 1999-10-10 (Box 8, Item 718_0249)
- 2 Hour Special on Emma Lazarus, 1999-10-17 (Box 7, Item 718_0239)
- Marathon Show: Mike Wishnie, Shirley Romaine [1999-070], 1999-10-17 (Box 7, Item 718_0242)
- Emma Lazarus Marathon, Part 1 [1999-026], 1999-10-17 (Box 13, Item 718_0440)
- Emma Lazarus Marathon, Part 2 [1999-027], 1999-10-17 (Box 13, Item 718_0441)
- Emma Lazarus Marathon, Part 3 [1999-028], 1999-10-17 (Box 13, Item 718_0442)
- Emma Lazarus Marathon: The Statue of Liberty - Its Meaning [1999-001], 1999-10-17 (Box 21, Item 718_0939)
- A: Update on Israel/Palestine with Gila Svirsky and Gershon Baskin; Marshall Meyer Awarding Honoring the CUNY Struggle / B: Allegra Pacheco on Israeli Supreme Court Decision on Torture; Karen Brodkin on Jews and Whiteness [1999-076], 1999 October 31; 1999 November 7 (Box 8, Item 718_0248)
- Update on Israel/Palestine with Gila Svirsky and Gershon Baskin; Marshall Meyer Awarding Honoring the CUNY Struggle; Andy Stettner and Dillona Lewis; Abraham Polansky [1999-040], 1999-10-31 (Box 13, Item 718_0454)
- Ocean Hill-Brownsville Dub, Part 1 [1999-006], 1999-11-11 (Box 12, Item 718_0427)
- Jeremy Burton on Hillary Clinton; Glen Busch, Iris Baez, and Richie Perez on Police Brutality Cases; Alicia Svigals and Elizabeth Ziff on Jewish Women, Lesbians, and Music [1999-074], 1999-11-14 (Box 7, Item 718_0246)
- Jeremy Burton on Hillary Clinton; Glen Busch, Iris Baez, and Richie Perez on Police Brutality Cases; Alicia Svigals and Elizabeth Ziff on Jewish Women, Lesbians, and Music (Partial Show) [1999-092], 1999-11-14 (Box 13, Item 718_0459)
- Charles Williams and Oliver Koppell on District 10 County School Board; Blanche Wiesen Cook on Eleanor Roosevelt, Vol. 2 [1999-009], 1999-11-21 (Box 12, Item 718_0430)
- Daniel Singer on Austrian and Swiss Far Right Victories; Alisse Waterston on Love, Sorrow, and Rage; Mary Brosnahan on Giuliani's Homeless Crackdown; Jim Hoberman on the Russian Film Festival; Gil Marks on Book The World of Jewish Cooking; David Gitlitz and Linda Davidson on Book A Drizzle of Honey; Jordan Elgrably Interview [1999-064], 1999 November 28; 1999 December 5 (Box 7, Item 718_0236)
- Daniel Singer on Austrian and Swiss Far Right Victories; Mary Brosnahan on Giuliani's Homeless Crackdown [1999-073], 1999 November 28 (Box 7, Item 718_0245)
- Daniel Singer on Austrian and Swiss Far Right Victories; Alisse Waterston on Love, Sorrow, and Rage; Mary Brosnahan on Giuliani's Homeless Crackdown [1999-008], 1999-11-28 (Box 12, Item 718_0429)
- Hanukkah Show with Jim Hoberman on the Russian Film Festival; Gil Marks on Book The World of Jewish Cooking [1999-062], 1999-12-05 (Box 7, Item 718_0234)
- Hanukkah Show [1999-029], 1999-12-05 (Box 13, Item 718_0443)
- A: Jack Foner Obituary; Hidden Jews of New Mexico, Parts 2 and 3 / B: Mark and Rhoda Berenson on Lori Berenson's Incarceration; Kathryn Hellerstein on Katya Molodovsky [1999-061], 1999 December 12; 1999 December 19 (Box 7, Item 718_0233)
- Parts 2 and 3 Hidden Jews of New Mexico; On Lori Berenson's Incarceration [1999-063], 1999 December 12; 1999 December 19 (Box 7, Item 718_0235)
- Mark and Rhoda Berenson on Lori Berenson; Kathryn Hellerstein on Katya Molodovsky [1999-039], 1999-12-12 (Box 13, Item 718_0453)
- Jack Foner Obituary; Hidden Jews of New Mexico, Parts 2 and 3, 1999-12-19 (Box 12, Item 718_0424)
- Ocean Hill-Brownsville, Parts 1 and 2 [1999-057], 1999-12-26 (Box 7, Item 718_0229)
- Ocean Hill-Brownsville, Part 1 [1999-011], 1999-12-26 (Box 12, Item 718_0432)
- Ocean Hill-Brownsville, Part 1 (cont'd) and Part 2 [1999-012], 1999-12-26 (Box 12, Item 718_0433)
- Jafar (Continued); Ronen Wolf of Ta'ayush; Amal Alnasasra, Bedouin Activist; Soosia Area of 10F Destruction; Meeting in Yatta to Plan Convoy [2015-019], circa 2000-2013 (Box 20, Item 718_1017)
- Summer Nights '00 at the Jewish Museum [2000-048], Summer 2000 (Box 14, Item 718_0484)
- Meeting in Yatta (Track 1) - Tracks Recorded in Israel/Palestine During Second Intifada [2015-020], circa 2000-2005 (Box 20, Item 718_1014)
- Diallo Protest [2000-090-z] (Box 21, Item 718_0944)
- Palestinian and Israeli Women's Peace Activism with Gila Svirsky and Isla Hajad [2015-003], circa 2000-2007 (Box 23, Item 718_0992)
- A: Millennium Show / B: Andy Stettner on Diallo Trial [2000-009], 2000 January 2; 2000 February 13 (Box 8, Item 718_0272)
- A: Millennium Show / B: Andy Stettner on Diallo Trial; Larry Cohler-Esses on Daycare Voucher Scandal; Melvin Jules Bukiet on Neurotica [2000-14], 2000 February 13; 2000 January 2 (Box 8, Item 718_0277)
- Millenium Show [2000-070], 2000-01-02 (Box 14, Item 718_0506)
- A: Jewish Film Festival with Aviva Weintraub and Richard Pena / B: Adrienne Cooper on "The Memoirs of Gluckel of Hameln" [2000-005], 2000 January 9; 2000 January 30 (Box 8, Item 718_0268)
- A: Aviva Kempner on The Life and Times of Hank Greenberg Film; Jewish Film Festival with Aviva Weintraub and Richard Pena / B: Adrienne Cooper on "The Memoirs of Gluckel of Hameln"; Shelley Hirsch on "My Father Piece"; Andy Ingall and Stacy Woolf on "Viva La Diva: Jewish Superstars of Song" Lecture [2000-21], 2000 January 9; 2000 January 30 (Box 9, Item 718_0284)
- Aviva Kempner on The Life and Times of Hank Greenberg Film; Jewish Film Festival with Aviva Weintraub and Richard Pena [2000-045], 2000-01-09 (Box 13, Item 718_0481)
- Adrienne Cooper on "The Memoirs of Gluckel of Hameln"; Shelley Hirsch on "My Father Piece"; Andy Ingall and Stacy Woolf on "Viva La Diva: Jewish Superstars of Song" Lecture [2000-039], 2000-01-30 (Box 13, Item 718_0475)
- A: Rabbis' Letter on Jerusalem; Michel Warschawski on Lebanon Bombing / B: Discussion of Jörg Haider [2000-15], 2000 February 6; 2000 February 20 (Box 8, Item 718_0278)
- A: Jerome Siegel on 100 Rabbis' Letter; Michel Warschawski on Lebanon Bombing; Megan Ortiz with Updates on Diallo Trial; David Espar on Lost Tribes of Israel / B: Discussion of Jörg Haider (Partial); Andy Statman on Mountain Jewish Music; Avi Shlaim on Israel and Arabs [2000-16], 2000 February 6; 2000 February 20 (Box 8, Item 718_0279)
- Michael Alpert on Jewish Mountain Music of the Caucasus; Avi Shlaim on Iron Wall (Partial) [2000-054], 2000-02-06 (Box 14, Item 718_0490)
- Andy Stettner on Diallo Trial; Larry Cohler-Esses on Daycare Voucher Scandal; Melvin Jules Bukiet on Neurotica [2000-067], 2000-02-13 (Box 14, Item 718_0503)
- Jerome Siegel on Rabbis' Letter; Michel Warschawski on Jerusalem; Megan Ortiz on Diallo Trial; David Espar on Lost Tribes of Israel [2000-068], 2000-02-20 (Box 14, Item 718_0504)
- Andy Stettner on Diallo Verdict; Emily Bilski on Berlin Metropolis Exhibition at the Jewish Museum; Ruth Messinger on AJWS Project for Women in Afghanistan [2000-18], 2000-02-27 (Box 8, Item 718_0281)
- A: Andy Stettner on Diallo Verdict; Ruth Messinger on AJWS Project for Women in Afghanistan / B: Peretz Kidron at the Jerusalem: A City of Two People's Festival; Human Rights Watch Film Festival with Nurit Kedar [2000-24], 2000 February 27; 2000 June 18 (Box 9, Item 718_0287)
- Andy Stettner on Diallo Verdict; Emily Bilski on Berlin Metropolis Exhibition at the Jewish Museum; Karl Heinz Muller on Kurt Weill's The Eternal Road; Ruth Messinger on Educating Girls Under the Taliban [2000-077], 2000-02-27 (Box 14, Item 718_0513)
- A: Emma Lazarus / B: John Brown 2000 with Matt Meyer, Laura Whitehorn, and Paul Buhle; Workmen's Circle 110th Anniversary with Nancy Sinkoff and Mark Mlotek; JFREJ Mock Bet Din [2000-002], 2000 March 5; 2000 May 7 (Box 8, Item 718_0265)
- A: Emma Lazarus / B: John Brown 2000; Workmen's Circle Anniversary [2000-19], 2000 March 5; 2000 May 7 (Box 9, Item 718_0282)
- Emma Lazarus with Nan Rubin [2000-055], 2000-03-05 (Box 14, Item 718_0491)
- Emma Lazarus [2000-088-z], 2000-03-05 (Box 34, Item 718_1003)
- A: Richie Perez and Ron Daniels on Police Policy after Diallo; Irving/Lipstadt Holocaust Denial Libel Trial / B: Arthur Strimling on Letter from Rudy Giuliani; Bob Hughes and Norm Fruchter on CFE trial; Tony Kushner Purimspiel; Richard Goldstein on Hans Haacke [2000-001], 2000 March 12; 2000 March 20 (Box 8, Item 718_0264)
- Irving/Lipstadt Holocaust Denial Libel Trial; Police Brutality and Actions [2000-052], 2000-03-12 (Box 14, Item 718_0488)
- A: Joan Lum, Raquel Grande, Basia Makowska on "Ain't I a Woman?" Conference; Jimmy Allen and Professor Leon Litwack on Without Sanctuary: Lynching Photography in America Exhibition / B: Rabbi Liever on Reform Movement Stance on Gay Marriage; Barbara Bowen on Spring PSC-CUNY Elections; Stanley Aronowitz on The Knowledge Factory; Cindy Greenberg on April 15 Demonstration after Diallo Verdict [2000-13], 2000 March 13; 2000 April 2 (Box 8, Item 718_0276)
- Purim Show; Rich Goldstein on Hans Haacke at Whitney [2000-046], 2000-03-19 (Box 13, Item 718_0482)
- A: "Ain't I a Woman?" Conference / B: Rabbi Liever on Reform Movement Stance on Gay Marriage [2000-20], 2000 March 26; 2000 April 2 (Box 9, Item 718_0283)
- "Ain't I a Woman?" Conference; Without Sanctuary: Lynching Photography in America Exhibition [2000-053], 2000-03-26 (Box 14, Item 718_0489)
- Reform Movement Stance on Gay Marriage; CUNY Union Elections; Stanley Aronowitz on The Knowledge Factory Book; Cindy Greenberg on Police Brutality Protest (Partial) [2000-047], 2000-04-02 (Box 13, Item 718_0483)
- A: 25th Anniversary of Vietnam Peace / B: Ziad Abbas, Amy Goodman [2000-007], 2000 April 16; 2000 April 23 (Box 8, Item 718_0270)
- A: Update on Palestinian Refugees with Ziad Abbas; Live Report from IMF/World Bank Demonstrations with Amy Goodman; Seder Readings by Ellen Lippmann, Michael Lerner, et al. / B: Leslie Cagan, 25th anniversary of the Peace in Vietnam; U.S. Holocaust Memorial Museum Symposium on Nazis and Homosexuals with Peter Black; Shapiro and Smith Dance Performance at Symphony Space with Daniel Shapiro [2000-10], 2000 April 16; 2000 April 23 (Box 8, Item 718_0273)
- Marathon Special, Adrienne Cooper, Ghetto Tango, Part 3 [2000-004], 2000-04-21 (Box 8, Item 718_0267)
- U.S. Holocaust Memorial Museum Symposium on Nazis and Homosexuals with Peter Black; Shapiro and Smith Dance Performance at Symphony Space with Daniel Shapiro [2000-076], 2000-04-23 (Box 14, Item 718_0512)
- A: "Mission Impossible" Youth Theater Performance; Holocaust Reparations for the Roma / B: Marathon: Theater in Holocaust [2000-003], 2000 April 30; 2000 May 21 (Box 8, Item 718_0266)
- "Mission Impossible" Youth Theater Performance; Holocaust Reparations for the Roma [2000-80-z], 2000-04-30 (Box 13, Item 718_0468)
- JFREJ Mock Bet Din; John Brown 2000; Workmen's Circle 100th Anniversary [2000-056], 2000-05-07 (Box 14, Item 718_0492)
- Marathon, Parts 2 and 3 (Partial) [2000-0056], 2000-05-21 (Box 8, Item 718_0269)
- Marathon, Adrienne Cooper, Ghetto Tango, Parts 2 of 3 [2000-032], 2000-05-21 (Box 9, Item 718_0295)
- Marathon Special: Ghetto Tango, Theatrical Performance During the Holocaust, Part 1 [2000-057], 2000-05-21 (Box 14, Item 718_0493)
- Marathon Special: Ghetto Tango, Theatrical Performance During the Holocaust, Part 2 (Partial) [2000-058], 2000-05-21 (Box 14, Item 718_0494)
- Marathon Special: Ghetto Tango, Theatrical Performance During the Holocaust, Part 3 (Partial) [2000-059], 2000-05-21 (Box 14, Item 718_0495)
- Israel Withdraws from Lebanon; Alice Mattison on The Book Borrower; Scottsboro Boys Documentary [2000-051], 2000-05-28 (Box 14, Item 718_0487)
- Uriya Shavit on Bashar Assad; Steve Block on NJ Public School Lawsuit; June 13 Rally for Quality Public Education; Jonathan Boyarin on the Jewish Community Center (JCC) Panel The Jew and the Camera [2000-25], 2000-06-11 (Box 9, Item 718_0288)
- A: Uriya Shavit on Bashar Assad; Steve Block on NJ Public School Lawsuit; June 13 Rally for Quality Public Education; Jonathan Boyarin on the JCC Panel The Jew and the Camera / B: Gay Pride Show [2000-26], 2000 June 11; 2000 June 25 (Box 9, Item 718_0289)
- Assad's Death; Rally for Quality Public Education; The Jew and the Camera Panel on Film [2000-050], 2000-06-11 (Box 14, Item 718_0486)
- Alternative Jerusalem Day; Police-Out-of-Schools Demonstration; Human Rights Film Festival (Partial) [2000-075], 2000-06-18 (Box 14, Item 718_0511)
- Gay Pride Show with Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Moisés Kaufman, and Faye Schulman [2000-060], 2000-06-25 (Box 14, Item 718_0496)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz and Maurice Berger on White Lies [2000-072], 2000-07-16 (Box 14, Item 718_0508)
- A: Martin Duberman on Left Out; Aaron Taub Interview with Edna Nachson on Book Yiddish Proletarian Theatre; Matt Rubin on RNC Protests / B: Igal Sarna on Peace Negotiations Between Israel and Palestine; Jennifer Bleyer and Lori Zimmerman on Philadelphia GOP National Convention Demonstration; Julie Davids and Kai Lumumba-Barrow on Philadelphia Fight on Police [2000-037], 2000 July 30; 2000 August 6 (Box 9, Item 718_0300)
- Martin Duberman on Left Out; Aaron Taub Interview with Edna Nachson on Book Yiddish Proletarian Theatre; Matt Rubin on RNC Protests [2000-083-z], 2000-07-30 (Box 13, Item 718_0472)
- Igal Sarna on Middle East Peace Process; Lori Zimmerman, Julie Davids, and Kai Lumumba-Barrow on Philadelphia Activism [2000-061], 2000-08-06 (Box 14, Item 718_0497)
- A: Lisa Hostein on Jews in the GOP, Jeremy Burton on the Lieberman VP choice / B: LA DNC Report with Jennifer Bleyer, Steve Rohde, Nan Rubin on Lower East Side synagogues [2000-036], 2000 August 13; 2000 August 20 (Box 9, Item 718_0299)
- Lisa Hostein on Jews in GOP; Jeremy Burton on Joseph Lieberman Nomination [2000-043], 2000-08-13 (Box 13, Item 718_0479)
- Jennifer Bleyer on DNC in LA; Nan Rubin on Lower East Side Synagogues [2000-040], 2000-08-20 (Box 13, Item 718_0476)
- Brooklyn Renaissance Plaza Strike with Carmen Reyes and Juana Mejia, Local 32BJ of SEIU [2000-089-z], 2000-09-01 (Box 21, Item 718_0942)
- A: 1st anniversary Gidon Busch killing with Jennifer Bleyer, Phyllis Bennis on Iraq sanctions, On Eagle's Wings conference on Yemenite Jews with Nitza Druyan and Dr. Bernie Kraut / B: NYS Senate race between Roy Goodman and Liz Krueger; Phyllis Bennis on roles of US, UN in Israel/Palestine crisis [2000-033], 2000 August 27; 2000 October 29 (Box 9, Item 718_0296)
- Jennifer Bleyer on Gidone Busch Killing; Phyllis Bennis on 10 Years of Iraq Sanctions; Yemeni Jewish Conference [2000-0832-z], 2000-08-27 (Box 13, Item 718_0471)
- Brooklyn Renaissance Plaza Strike with Carmen Reyes and Juana Mejia, Local 32BJ of SEIU [2000-089-z], 2000-09-01 (Box 21, Item 718_0943)
- A: Mike Cinquina, MoMA strike, Jim Bracchitta on SAG strike, Manny Ness on deli organizing effort, Carmen Reyes and Juana Mejia on Brooklyn Renaissance Plaza strike / B: Amira Sohl on Palestinian refugee march, Rachel Bernstein, Harriet Tanzman on Selma vote harassment, Sarah Blustain on Dr. Laura [2000-034], 2000 September 3; 2000 September 10 (Box 9, Item 718_0297)
- Labor Day Show [2000-044], 2000-09-03 (Box 13, Item 718_0480)
- Amira Sohl on Palestinian Refugee March; Rachel Bernstein Exhibition; Harriet Tanzman on Corruption and Harassment in Selma Mayoral Race; Sarah Blustain on Dr. Laura Schlessinger [2000-066], 2000-09-10 (Box 14, Item 718_0502)
- A: Ellen Willis and Richard Goldstein in the Village Voice on the Gore Nader debate; Sam Day on Mordechai Vanunu / B: Eve Soderman on the new Jewish Museum in Berlin, Egal Ezraty on the Arab-Hebrew Theater of Jaffa, Michael Zweig on "The Working Class Majority" [2000-035], 2000 September 17; 2000 September 24 (Box 9, Item 718_0298)
- Eve Soderman on New Jewish Museum in Berlin; Egal Ezraty on the Arab-Hebrew Theatre of Jaffa; Michael Zweig on New Book, The Work Class Majority [2000-035], 2000-09-17 (Box 13, Item 718_0470)
- Richard Goldstein and Ellen Willis on Gore vs. Nader; Sam Day on Vanunu Conference [2000-049], 2000-09-24 (Box 14, Item 718_0485)
- JFREJ Tashlich [2000-091-z], 2000-09-24 (Box 21, Item 718_0945)
- Rosh Hashanah Tashlich, Steve Benen on Christian Coalition's Convention, Artist Martha Rosler / B: Palestinian-Israeli blowup, Adam Keller, Nabila Espanioly, Rashid Khalidi [2000-031], 2000-10-01-2000-10-08 (Box 9, Item 718_0294)
- JFREJ Activist Tashlich; Christian Coalition Conference; Political Artist, Martha Rosler [2000-081-z], 2000-10-01 (Box 13, Item 718_0469)
- Al-Aqsa Intifada Highlights, with Introduction by Adam Keller, Nabila Espanioly, and Rashid Khalidi Introduction, Part 1 [2000-092-z], 2000-10-08 (Box 21, Item 718_0941)
- Marathon, Side 2 [2000-029], 2000-10-22 (Box 9, Item 718_0292)
- Marathon, Sides 1 and 3 [2000-030], 2000-10-22 (Box 9, Item 718_0293)